(window.webpackJsonp=window.webpackJsonp||[]).push([[0],[,,function(e){e.exports=[{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20hero%20in%20the%2080s%20animated%20video%20game%20%27Dragon%27s%20Lair%27%3F",correct_answer:"Dirk%20the%20Daring",incorrect_answers:["Arthur","Sir%20Toby%20Belch","Guy%20of%20Gisbourne"]},{category:"Animals",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20for%20modern%20day%20humans%3F",correct_answer:"Homo%20Sapiens",incorrect_answers:["Homo%20Ergaster","Homo%20Erectus","Homo%20Neanderthalensis"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Books",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"What%20is%20Ron%20Weasley%27s%20middle%20name%3F",correct_answer:"Bilius",incorrect_answers:["Arthur","John","Dominic"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Comics",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"Who%20is%20the%20creator%20of%20the%20comic%20series%20%22The%20Walking%20Dead%22%3F",correct_answer:"Robert%20Kirkman",incorrect_answers:["Stan%20Lee","Malcolm%20Wheeler-Nicholson","Robert%20Crumb"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Board%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"At%20the%20start%20of%20a%20standard%20game%20of%20the%20Monopoly%2C%20if%20you%20throw%20a%20double%20six%2C%20which%20square%20would%20you%20land%20on%3F",correct_answer:"Electric%20Company",incorrect_answers:["Water%20Works","Chance","Community%20Chest"]},{category:"Geography",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Jamaica%3F",correct_answer:"Kingston",incorrect_answers:["Rio%20de%20Janeiro","Dar%20es%20Salaam","Kano"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"When%20did%20Jamaica%20recieve%20its%20independence%20from%20England%3F%20",correct_answer:"1962",incorrect_answers:["1492","1963","1987"]},{category:"Animals",type:"boolean",difficulty:"easy",question:"Kangaroos%20keep%20food%20in%20their%20pouches%20next%20to%20their%20children.",correct_answer:"False",incorrect_answers:["True"]},{category:"General%20Knowledge",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"In%202013%20how%20much%20money%20was%20lost%20by%20Nigerian%20scams%3F",correct_answer:"%2412.7%20Billion",incorrect_answers:["%2495%20Million","%24956%20Million","%242.7%20Billion"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"How%20old%20was%20Lyndon%20B.%20Johnson%20when%20he%20assumed%20the%20role%20of%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F",correct_answer:"55",incorrect_answers:["50","60","54"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"In%20World%20of%20Warcraft%20lore%2C%20who%20organized%20the%20creation%20of%20the%20Paladins%3F",correct_answer:"Alonsus%20Faol",incorrect_answers:["Uther%20the%20Lightbringer","Alexandros%20Mograine","Sargeras%2C%20The%20Daemon%20Lord"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"boolean",difficulty:"medium",question:"In%20the%20game%20%22Subnautica%22%2C%20a%20%22Cave%20Crawler%22%20will%20attack%20you.",correct_answer:"True",incorrect_answers:["False"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20device%20that%20allows%20for%20infinite%20energy%20in%20the%20anime%20%22Dimension%20W%22%3F",correct_answer:"Coils",incorrect_answers:["Wires","Collectors","Tesla"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Cream%20the%20Rabbit%27s%20mom%20in%20the%20%22Sonic%20the%20Hedgehog%22%20series%3F",correct_answer:"Vanilla",incorrect_answers:["Peach","Strawberry","Mint"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"easy",question:"These%20two%20countries%20held%20a%20commonwealth%20from%20the%2016th%20to%2018th%20century.",correct_answer:"Poland%20and%20Lithuania",incorrect_answers:["Hutu%20and%20Rwanda","North%20Korea%20and%20South%20Korea","Bangladesh%20and%20Bhutan"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Television",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"Which%20of%20these%20voices%20wasn%27t%20a%20choice%20for%20the%20House%20AI%20in%20%22The%20Simpsons%20Treehouse%20of%20Horror%22%20short%2C%20House%20of%20Whacks%3F",correct_answer:"George%20Clooney",incorrect_answers:["Matthew%20Perry","Dennis%20Miller","Pierce%20Brosnan"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Music",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"From%20which%20album%20is%20the%20Gorillaz%20song%2C%20%22On%20Melancholy%20Hill%22%20featured%20in%3F",correct_answer:"Plastic%20Beach",incorrect_answers:["Demon%20Days","Humanz","The%20Fall"]},{category:"General%20Knowledge",type:"boolean",difficulty:"easy",question:"Scotland%20voted%20to%20become%20an%20independent%20country%20during%20the%20referendum%20from%20September%202014.",correct_answer:"False",incorrect_answers:["True"]},{category:"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",type:"multiple",difficulty:"medium",question:"In%20Left%204%20Dead%2C%20which%20campaign%20has%20the%20protagonists%20going%20through%20a%20subway%20in%20order%20to%20reach%20a%20hospital%20for%20evacuation%3F",correct_answer:"No%20Mercy",incorrect_answers:["Subway%20Sprint","Hospital%20Havoc","Blood%20Harvest"]},{category:"History",type:"multiple",difficulty:"hard",question:"What%20was%20the%20last%20colony%20the%20UK%20ceded%20marking%20the%20end%20of%20the%20British%20Empire%3F",correct_answer:"Hong%20Kong",incorrect_answers:["India","Australia","Ireland"]}]},,,function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(16)},,,,,,function(e,t,n){},function(e,t,n){},function(e,t,n){},function(e,t,n){},function(e,t,n){},function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var a=n(0),r=n.n(a),o=n(4),c=n.n(o),i=(n(11),n(1)),s=(n(12),function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:0,t=arguments.length>1&&void 0!==arguments[1]?arguments[1]:0;return t?Math.round(e/t*100):0}),l=function(e){var t=e.currentQuestionIndex,n=e.totalQuestions,a=t<=n?s(t,n):100;return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"overall-progress",style:{width:"".concat(a,"%"),transition:"width .6s ease"}})},u=(n(13),function(e){var t=e.currentQuestionIndex,n=e.totalQuestions,o=e.question,c=e.updateCurrentQuestionIndex,s=e.updateScore,l=e.updateScoreIndex,u=Object(a.useState)([]),m=Object(i.a)(u,2),d=m[0],h=m[1],y=Object(a.useState)(""),f=Object(i.a)(y,2),w=f[0],p=f[1];Object(a.useEffect)(function(){var e=[];if("boolean"===o.type)e=["True","False"];else{var t=Math.floor(Math.random()*(o.incorrect_answers||[]).length+1);(e=o.incorrect_answers||[]).length&&e.splice(t,0,o.correct_answer)}h(e)},[o.correct_answer,o.incorrect_answers,o.type]);var g="easy"===o.difficulty?"gray":"black",E="hard"===o.difficulty?"black":"gray",b=w?"disable-answer":"";return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-container"},r.a.createElement("h2",null,"Question ",t," of ",n),r.a.createElement("small",{className:"category"},decodeURIComponent(o.category)),r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement("span",{className:"difficulty black"},"\u2605"),r.a.createElement("span",{className:"difficulty ".concat(g)},"\u2605"),r.a.createElement("span",{className:"difficulty ".concat(E)},"\u2605")),r.a.createElement("p",{className:"question"},decodeURIComponent(o.question)),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"answers"},d.map(function(e,t){return r.a.createElement("button",{className:"answer ".concat(b,"\n            ").concat(w===e?"selected-answer":w&&e===o.correct_answer?"correct-answer":""," "),key:t,disabled:""!==w,onClick:function(){return function(e){p(e),l(),e===o.correct_answer&&s()}(e)}},decodeURIComponent(e))})),""!==w?r.a.createElement("div",{className:"text-center"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"correct-sorry"},w===o.correct_answer?"Correct!":"Sorry!"),r.a.createElement("button",{className:"next-question",onClick:function(){return c(),void p("")}},"Next Question")):null)}),m=(n(14),function(e){var t=e.totalQuestions,n=e.score,a=e.currentScoreIndex,o=s(n,t),c=s(n,a),i=function(e,t,n){return s(e-t+n,e)}(t,a,n);return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"score"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-container"},r.a.createElement("span",null,"Score: ",c,"%"),r.a.createElement("span",null,"Max Score: ",i,"%")),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-bar"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"max-score-bar",style:{width:"".concat(i,"%"),transition:"width .6s ease"}}),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"current-score-bar",style:{width:"".concat(c,"%"),transition:"width .6s ease"}}),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"lowest-score-bar",style:{width:"".concat(o,"%"),transition:"width .6s ease"}})))}),d=n(2);n(15);var h=function(){var e=Object(a.useState)({}),t=Object(i.a)(e,2),n=t[0],o=t[1],c=Object(a.useState)(0),s=Object(i.a)(c,2),h=s[0],y=s[1],f=Object(a.useState)(0),w=Object(i.a)(f,2),p=w[0],g=w[1],E=Object(a.useState)(0),b=Object(i.a)(E,2),_=b[0],v=b[1],S=d.length;return Object(a.useEffect)(function(){o(d[h])},[h]),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"App"},r.a.createElement(l,{currentQuestionIndex:h+1,totalQuestions:S}),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"quiz-container"},h<S&&r.a.createElement(u,{currentQuestionIndex:h+1,totalQuestions:S,question:n,updateCurrentQuestionIndex:function(){return y(h+1)},updateScore:function(){return g(p+1)},updateScoreIndex:function(){return v(_+1)}}),h===S&&r.a.createElement("div",{className:"text-center"},r.a.createElement("h1",null,"Quiz Completed"),r.a.createElement("h2",null,"Score ",Math.floor(100*p/S),"%"),r.a.createElement("h2",null,"Score ","".concat(p," / ").concat(S))),r.a.createElement(m,{totalQuestions:S,score:p,currentScoreIndex:_})))};Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));c.a.render(r.a.createElement(h,null),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then(function(e){e.unregister()})}],[[5,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.f7e3df23.chunk.js.map